Guide to the Alfred Stieglitz / Georgia O'Keeffe Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alfred Stieglitz: Correspondence, 1874-1950; Series I; 40.4; (97 boxes)
  - PERSONAL AND BUSINESS CORRESPONDENCE
    - Read, Frank H., 1910-11 (Box 40, Folder 963)
    - Redfield, Robert S., 1900-07 (Box 40, Folder 964)
      See also: Alfred Horsley Hinton (1899), Box 24, folders 573-576
    - Reed, John
      See: Harriet M. Olcott, Box 37, folder 894
    - Reedy, William Marion, 1913 (Box 40, Folder 965)
    - Rehm, Mary Torr, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 966)
    - Reid, Harry B.
      See: Camera Club of New York, Box 8, folder 202
    - Reiner, H. C.
      See: M. A. Seed Dry Plate Company, Box 32, folder 748
    - Reinhardt Galleries, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 967)
    - Reissinger, Robert
      See: Camera-Klub, Wien, Box 9, folder 205
    - Rey, Guido, 1907-08 (Box 40, Folder 968)
    - Rhoades, Carol N., 1915 Jun 3 (Box 40, Folder 969)
    - Rhoades, Katharine Nash, 1911-22 (Box 40, Folder 970-978)
    - Rhoades, Katharine Nash, 1923-39, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 979-982)
    - Rhode Island School of Design, 1911 Nov 7 (Box 41, Folder 983)
    - Rich, Daniel Catton
    - Ridge, Lola
    - Riley, A. M.
    - Ringel, Frederick Julius, 1932-43 (Box 41, Folder 984)
      See also: Box 98, Folder 1927
    - Rittenhouse Press, Inc.
      See: A. K. Boursault, Box 5, folder 130
      See: John Nilsen Laurvik, Box 30, folder 701
    - Rivera, Diego, 1933-34 (Box 41, Folder 985)
    - Robinson, Florence H.
      See: Sweet Briar College, Box 49, folder 1156
    - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich, 1931 Feb 13 (Box 41, Folder 986)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson
    - Rodakiewicz, Henwar, 1932-42, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 987-988)
    - Rodakiewicz, Peggy
      See: Margaret Kiskadden, Box 28, folder 660
    - Rodin, Auguste, 1911, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 989)
    - Rodman, Selden
      See: Common Sense, Box 10, folder 247
    - Rogers and Company, 1908-17, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 990)
    - Rohe, Wilhelm K., 1908-10, 1921 (Box 41, Folder 991)
    - Rönnebeck, Arnold, 1919-45 (Box 41, Folder 992-993)
    - Rood, Roland, 1906 (Box 41, Folder 994)
      See also: Joseph Keiley (1904-06), Box 27, folders 635-644
    - Rosenbaum, Walter, 1913-16 (Box 41, Folder 995)
    - Rosenblum, Walter
      See: Nancy Newhall, Box 37, folder 870
    - Rosenfeld, Paul: precis of letters (Box 41, Folder 996)
    - Rosenfeld, Paul: correspondence, 1915-22 (Box 41, Folder 997-998)
    - Rosenfeld, Paul: correspondence, 1923-45, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 999-1003)
      See also: Sherwood Anderson (1930), Box 2, folders 35-45
      See also: Ida O'Keeffe (1925), Box 37, folders 889-892
      See also: Museum of Modern Art (1936), Box 36, folders 847-848
    - Roshanara, 1914 Jun 17 (Box 42, Folder 1004)
    - Ross, Cary: precis of letters, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1005)
    - Ross, Cary: correspondence, 1931-42, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1006-1009)
    - Ross, Cary: letter to Dorothy Norman, 1933 Sep 20 (Box 42, Folder 1010)
    - Rossin, Alfred S. and Clara, 1925-28 (Box 43, Folder 1011)
    - Rothschild, Mr.
    - Royal Photographic Society of Great Britain, 1895-1924 (Box 43, Folder 1012)
      See also: Alvin L. Coburn (1914), Box 10, folders 236-240
      See also: J. Dudley Johnston, Box 26, folder 621
      See also: John C. Warburg, Box 50, folder 1218
    - Rubin, Reuven, 1922-28 (Box 43, Folder 1013)
    - Rubincam, Harry C., 1903-11 (Box 43, Folder 1014)
    - Rudolph, Joseph, 1927-29, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1015)
    - Rugg, Harold Ordway, 1931-41 (Box 43, Folder 1016)
    - Russell, Morgan, 1916-21 (Box 43, Folder 1017)
      See also: Macdonald-Wright, Stanton: correspondence (1920), box 33
    - "S" general, 1898-1946, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1018-1019)
    - Sachs, Paul J.
    - Sage, Cornelia Bentley
    - Saint-Gaudens, Homer
      See: Carnegie Institute, Box 9, folder 219
    - St. Louis Art Museum, 1906, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 1020)
    - St. Mark's Church in-the-Bowery (New York, N. Y.), 1912 Jun 14 (Box 43, Folder 1021)
    - Salon Photographique Bruxelles, 1895 Dec 2 (Box 43, Folder 1022)
    - San Francisco Art Association
    - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1944 Sep 27 (Box 43, Folder 1023)
    - San Francisco News Company, 1911-16 (Box 43, Folder 1024)
    - Sandburg, Carl, 1920-39 (Box 43, Folder 1025)
    - Sarter, Emilie, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 1026)
    - Sawyer, Charles H.
    - Sayer, Evelyn, 1913, 1916, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1027)
    - Schamberg, Morton Livingston, 1916, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1028)
    - Schauffler, Florence M.; Schauffler, Charles E., 1916-30, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1029-1030)
    - Schiller, M., 1915-20 (Box 43, Folder 1031)
    - School Art League of New York City, 1915, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1032)
    - Schram, Louis B.
    - Schulte, David; Schulte, Carrie E., 1928-30 (Box 43, Folder 1033)
    - Schumacher, Robert H., 1907-19, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1034)
    - Schütze, Eva Lawrence Watson, 1900-06, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1035-1036)
    - Schwab, Arthur
      See: Edna Clare Bryner, Box 8, folder 191
    - Scolik, Charles, 1889-91 (Box 43, Folder 1037)
    - Scott, Temple, 1911-21 (Box 43, Folder 1038)
    - Sears, Sarah C., n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1039)
    - Secession Munich
    - Seeley, George H., 1904-11, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1040-1041)
    - Seff, Manuel, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 1042)
    - Seldes, Gilbert
      See: Paul Rosenfeld (1923), Boxes 41-42, folders 997-1003
    - Seligman, Sylvan, 1937-38 (Box 44, Folder 1043)
    - Seligmann, Herbert J., 1918-26 (Box 44, Folder 1044-1052)
    - Seligmann, Herbert J., 1927-37 (Box 45, Folder 1053-1056)
      See also: Boni and Liveright, Box 5, folder 122
    - Seligmann, Herbert J.: correspondence with Dorothy Brett and Frieda Lawrence, 1931 (Box 45, Folder 1057)
    - Seligmann, Herbert J.: correspondence with The Nation, 1932 (Box 45, Folder 1058)
    - Seligmann, Lilias, 1923 (Box 45, Folder 1059)
    - The Seven Arts
      See: Waldo David Frank (1916), Box 20, folders 446-450
    - Severini, Gino, 1917-18 (Box 45, Folder 1060)
      See also: Walter Pach, Box 38, folder 902
    - Shadowland, 1921 (Box 45, Folder 1061)
    - Sharp, Elizabeth A., 1909, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1062)
    - Shaw, George Bernard, 1904 Jun 25 (Box 45, Folder 1063)
      See also: Frederick H. Evans (1903), Box 18, folders 412-413
    - Sheeler, Charles R., 1911-22, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1064)
    - Shelton Hotel, 1934-35 (Box 45, Folder 1065)
    - Sheppard, Kathleen, 1940, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1066)
    - Shreve, Adèle C., 1915, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1067)
      See also: Paul Strand (1919 Aug), Box 48, folders 1129-1145
    - The Shipley School, 1932 (Box 45, Folder 1068)
    - Simmons, Will, 1929, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1069)
    - Simonson, Lee, 1913-39 (Box 45, Folder 1070)
      Includes: a letter from Leo Stein, March 21, 1923 as an enclosure
      See also: John Marin (1928), Box 34, folders 778-788
    - Simpson, Kate, 1912 (Box 45, Folder 1071)
    - Singer, Hans W.
      See: Carl Zigrosser, Box 52, folder 1280
    - Skolfield, Raymond, 1932, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1072)
    - Sloan, John
      See: New York Call, Box 36, folder 860
    - Sloane, Dorothy, 1943-44, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1073)
    - Sloane, Thomas O'Conor, 1913, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1074)
      See also: Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, Box 38, folder 910
    - Smith, Adele K.
      See: Studio House, Box 49, folder 1153
    - Smith, Frank Eugene
      See: Frank Eugene, box 18, folders 407-409
    - Smith, Leonora, 1944 Aug 26 (Box 45, Folder 1075)
    - Smith, Pamela Colman, 1907-09 (Box 45, Folder 1076)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1911-24 (Box 45, Folder 1077)
    - Sneyers, Leon
    - Société Anonyme
      See: Katherine S. Dreier, Box 15, folder 349
      See: Marcel Duchamp, Box 15, folder 353
    - Society of Arts and Crafts of Detroit, 1910 (Box 45, Folder 1078)
    - Society of Friends of William Carlos Williams, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 1079)
    - Society of Independent Artists, Inc., 1917, 1941 (Box 45, Folder 1080)
      See also: Arthur Dove (1941 Mar), Boxes 13-15, folders 316-343
    - Solomon R. Guggenheim Foundation, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 1081)
    - Spencer, Ema, 1907-08 (Box 45, Folder 1082)
    - Sprinchorn, Carl, 1918 Jul 31 (Box 45, Folder 1083)
    - Stanbery, Katharine Sheward; Stanbery, Mary R., 1901-06 (Box 45, Folder 1084)
      See also: Clarence H. White (1901), Box 51, folders 1242-1245
    - Stecker, Esther and Louis, 1936-45 (Box 45, Folder 1085)
    - Steichen, Clara Smith: correspondence and poems, 1916-44, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1086-1088)
      See also: Kate Rodina Steichen, Box 46, folders 1104-1105
    - Steichen, Clara Smith: rejection letters from publishers, 1916 (Box 46, Folder 1089)
    - Steichen, Edward: precis of letters, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1090)
    - Steichen, Edward: correspondence, 1900-41, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1091-1097)
      Folder 1093 includes: letters from Adolf de Meyer dated Nov 11, 1906, Dec 3, 1906 and Dec 12, 1906 as enclosures
      Folder 1094 includes: a letter from Robert Demachy as an enclosure to Steichen letter of [Jun 1907]
      See also: F. Bruckmann K.G. (1911), Box 19, folders 420-423
      See also: Franz Goerke, Box 21, folder 486
      See also: Anne Morgan, Box 35, folder 830
    - Steichen, Edward: bills and receipts, 1909-17 (Box 46, Folder 1098)
    - Steichen, Edward: correspondence with Photo-Era, 1904 (Box 46, Folder 1099)
    - Steichen, Edward: letter to Gertrude Kasebier, 1902 Mar 27 (Box 46, Folder 1100)
    - Steichen, Edward: letter to Clara Steichen, 1917 Jan 17 (Box 46, Folder 1101)
    - Steichen, Edward: letter to Edward Stieglitz, 1907 May 3 (Box 46, Folder 1102)
    - Steichen, Edward: letter to Emmeline Stieglitz, ca. 1902 (Box 46, Folder 1103)
    - Steichen, Kate Rodina: poems, 1915-16 (Box 46a, Folder 1104)
    - Steichen, Kate Rodina: Stieglitz's copies of her poems, 1916 Mar (Box 46a, Folder 1105)
    - Steichen, Mary Kemp, 1906-22 (Box 46a, Folder 1106)
    - Stein, Gertrude, 1912-14, n.d. (Box 46a, Folder 1107)
    - Stein, Leo D., 1911-45, n.d. (Box 46a, Folder 1108)
      See also: Lee Simonson, Box 45, folder 1070
      See also: Paul Strand (1922), Box 48, folders 1129-1145
    - Steinhardt, Edna, 1910-13 (Box 47, Folder 1109)
    - Steinitz, Kate, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1110)
    - Steloff, Frances
      See: Gotham Book Mart, Box 21, folder 495
    - Stephany, Lewis F., 1903-07 (Box 47, Folder 1111)
    - Stern, Mrs. Abraham, 1915-27 (Box 47, Folder 1112)
    - Stern, Alfred K., 1935 (Box 47, Folder 1113)
    - Sterne, Maurice, 1915 Feb 6 (Box 47, Folder 1114)
    - Stettheimer, Ettie, 1918-45, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1115-1116)
    - Stettheimer, Florine, 1928-38 (Box 47, Folder 1117)
    - Stilwell, Elsie, 1935-41 (Box 47, Folder 1118-1119)
    - Stirling, Edmund, 1899-1908 (Box 47, Folder 1120-1123)
      Folder 1121 includes: a letter to Keiley from Stirling, Apr 25, 1901
    - Stokes, Walter P., 1902-03 (Box 47, Folder 1124)
    - Stokowski, Leopold
      See: Edgard Varèse, Box 50, folder 1202
    - Stoloff, Carolyn, 1944-46 (Box 47, Folder 1125)
    - Stouffs, Victor
    - Stovel, Rex, 1913, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1126)
    - Strand, Jack, 1929 Jan 21 (Box 47, Folder 1127)
    - Strand, Paul: precis of letters (Box 48, Folder 1128)
    - Strand, Paul: correspondence, 1916-40 (Box 48, Folder 1129-1145)
      Folder 1139 includes: typescript copy of letter of Jun 17, 1922 from Leo Stein
      Folder 1142 includes: Jul 29, 1924 letter from Rebecca Salsbury Strand
    - Strand, Paul: power of attorney, 1918 Mar 28 (Box 48, Folder 1146)
    - Strand, Rebecca Salsbury
      See: Rebecca Salsbury Strand James, Boxes 25-26, folders 607-614
    - Straus, Nathan, Jr.
      See: Puck, Box 39, folder 946
    - Strauss, Albert, 1882 (Box 49, Folder 1147)
    - Strauss, Helen, 1914 (Box 49, Folder 1148)
    - Strauss, John Francis, 1902-10 (Box 49, Folder 1149)
    - Strauss, Julius C., 1902-13 (Box 49, Folder 1150)
    - Struss, Karl, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 1151)
    - The Studio, 1904 (Box 49, Folder 1152)
    - Studio House, 1936-37 (Box 49, Folder 1153)
    - Subscription News Company, 1911 (Box 49, Folder 1154)
    - Sweeney, James Johnson; Sweeney, John, 1940-46 (Box 49, Folder 1155)
    - Sweet Briar College, 1941-43 (Box 49, Folder 1156)
    - Sykes, Gerald, 1929-42, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1157)
      Includes: typed copy of Oct 28, 1939 letter to Marin
    - "T" general, 1900-45, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1158)
    - T. & R. Annan & Sons
      See: J. Craig Annan, Box 3, folders 46-49
    - Talens & Zoon
      See: Arthur Dove (1932 Mar), Boxes 13-15, folders 316-343
    - Tellez, Juan
      See: Christian Brinton, Box 8, folder 176
    - Tennant, John A., 1902-29 (Box 49, Folder 1159)
    - Tennant, Pearl
      See: Mildred P. Wilson, Box 52, folders 1268-1269
    - Thayer, Scofield, 1925 Apr 13 (Box 49, Folder 1160)
      See also: Donald Litchfield, Box 31, folders 725-730 (1925 May)
    - Thibaudeau, Augustus, 1910-23 (Box 49, Folder 1161)
    - Thibaudeau, May A.: letter to Emmeline Stieglitz, 1910 Nov 8 (Box 49, Folder 1162)
    - Thompson, Arthur Ripley, 1940, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1163)
    - Thompson, Louis
      See: John Marin (1936), Box 34, folders 778-788
    - Timmins, George, 1895-1911, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1164)
    - Todd, Frederick Dundas, 1900-06, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1165)
      See also: Spencer Kellogg, Box 28, folder 649
    - Tofel, Jennings, 1923-39, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1166-1171)
    - Toledo Museum of Art, 1910, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 1172)
    - Toomer, Jean, 1924-44, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1173-1174)
    - Toomer, Marjorie
    - Török, Ervin; Török, Louise B., 1929-44 (Box 49, Folder 1175)
    - Toronto Camera Club, 1897 Apr 14 (Box 49, Folder 1176)
    - Torr, Helen, 1927-45 (Box 49, Folder 1177)
    - Totzke, Hans, 1884-1922 (Box 49, Folder 1178)
      Includes: letter to Hedwig Stieglitz
    - Trask, John E. D.
      See: Panama Pacific International Exposition, Box 38, folder 904
    - Traubel, Horace, 1910-18, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1179)
    - Troth, Henry, 1896-1902 (Box 50, Folder 1180)
    - Troubetzkoy, Pierre, 1921, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1181)
    - Troubetzkoy, Amélie Rives Chanler, 1904 Sep 19
    - True, Dorothy, 1920, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 1182)
    - Tschudy, Herbert B.
    - Turnbull, Grace, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1183)
    - Turner, Hermine, 1926-42 (Box 50, Folder 1184)
      Includes: notes from Emmeline Stieglitz
    - "U" general, 1910-45 (Box 50, Folder 1185)
    - Ulrich, Carl
    - Underwood, W. Orison, 1911-14 (Box 50, Folder 1186)
    - United States. Army Signal Corps., 1917 (Box 50, Folder 1187)
    - United States. Bureau of Internal Revenue., 1920-45 (Box 50, Folder 1188)
    - United States. Customs Service., 1910-13 (Box 50, Folder 1189)
    - United States. Department of Justice., 1915 (Box 50, Folder 1190)
    - United States. Postal Service., 1911, 1913 (Box 50, Folder 1191)
    - United States. Works Progress Administration., 1935, 1937 (Box 50, Folder 1192)
    - University of Minnesota, 1935-42 (Box 50, Folder 1193-1194)
    - University of North Carolina Press, 1927 (Box 50, Folder 1195)
    - "V" general, 1900-41, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1196)
    - Van Loan, Dorothy, 1937-45, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1197)
    - Van Noppen, Leonard Charles, 1909, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1198)
    - Van Vechten, Carl, 1933, 1935 (Box 50, Folder 1199)
    - Vander Veer, Edgar A., 1908 (Box 50, Folder 1200)
    - Vanity Fair, 1914-35 (Box 50, Folder 1201)
      See also: Anne Brigman (1915), Box 8, folders 169-173
      See also: Herbert Seligmann (1921 Sep), Boxes 44-45, folders 1044-1056
    - Varèse, Edgard, 1921-27 (Box 50, Folder 1202)
    - Varnum, Fred, 1909 May 29 (Box 50, Folder 1203)
    - Vaux, George, 1899-1902 (Box 50, Folder 1204)
      See also: Joseph Keiley (1901), Box 27, folders 635-644
    - Vienna Photo-Club
    - The Veltin School, 1911-16 (Box 50, Folder 1205)
    - Venturi, Lionello, 1943-46 (Box 50, Folder 1206)
    - Verdi, Hope Aspell, 1929 (Box 50, Folder 1207)
    - Vogel, J. W.
      See: Photographische Jubiläums-Ausstellung, Berlin, Box 39, folder 928
    - Volland, P. F.
      See: Edward Steichen (1903), Box 46, folders 1091-1097
    - Von Keller, Beatrice
    - "W" general, 1899-1946, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1208)
    - Wade, Elizabeth Flint, 1898, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1209)
    - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1933-43 (Box 50, Folder 1210)
    - Wahl, Margrit, 1923 (Box 50, Folder 1211)
    - The Walden School, 1923, 1927 (Box 50, Folder 1212)
    - Walker, Hudson D., 1940, 1944 (Box 50, Folder 1213)
    - Walker, Robert, 1929-36 (Box 50, Folder 1214)
    - Walker, Sybil, 1925-40, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1215)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham: correspondence, 1912-37 (Box 50, Folder 1216-1217)
      Folder 1216 includes: card to Emmeline Stieglitz
      Folder 1217 includes: typed copy of letter to Walkowitz from William Einstein
    - Warburg, John C., 1903-13 (Box 50, Folder 1218)
    - Ward, Henry Snowden, 1901-11 (Box 50, Folder 1219)
      See also: Anne Brigman (1910-11), Box 8, folders 169-173
    - Warner, Keith, 1940-46 (Box 50, Folder 1220-1221)
      Both folders include letters to Warner from Stanton Macdonald-Wright
    - Washburn, Gordon
    - Washburn, Kenneth
      See: Cornell University, Box 10, folder 255
    - Wasow, E.
      See: F. Bruckmann K.G. (1919), Box 19, folders 420-423
    - Watkins, C. Law
    - Watson, James Sibley, 1924-25 (Box 51, Folder 1222)
    - Watson Schütze, Eva Lawrence
      See: Eva Lawrence Watson Schütze, Box 43, folders 1035-1036
    - Webb, Todd, 1943-46 (Box 51, Folder 1223)
    - Weber, Max: correspondence, 1910-33, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1224)
    - Weber, Max: exhibition scheme and price list, 1911 (Box 51, Folder 1225)
    - Weber, Max: letters to others, 1911 (Box 51, Folder 1226)
    - Weber, Max: hints on color, drawing, landscape; lesson notes for Katherine Stieglitz Stearns, [1910] (Box 51, Folder 1227)
    - Wegener, Otto
      See: Edward Steichen (1906), Box 46, folders 1091-1097
    - Weichsel, John, 1913-18 (Box 51, Folder 1228)
    - Weil, Mathilde, 1901, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1229)
      See also: Edmund Stirling (1903), Box 47, folders 1120-1123
      See also: John Francis Strauss, Box 49, folder 1149
    - Weir, J. Alden, 1906 (Box 51, Folder 1230)
    - Wells, Cady, 1933-38 (Box 51, Folder 1231)
    - Wells Fargo & Company, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 1232)
    - Wertheim, Alma M.; Wertheim, Maurice, 1921-31 (Box 51, Folder 1233)
    - Weston, Edward, 1922-42 (Box 51, Folder 1234-1235)
    - Weston, Harold; Weston, Faith, 1926-34 (Box 51, Folder 1236)
    - Weyhe Gallery
      See: E. Weyhe, Box 16, folder 362
    - Wheeler, Emily, 1938, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 1237)
    - Wheeler, Mary C., 1916-18 (Box 51, Folder 1238)
    - Wheeler, Monroe
    - Wheelwright, Mary Colman, 1937, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1239)
    - Wherritt, Russell, 1909-15, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1240)
    - White, Clarence Hudson: precis of letters, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1241)
    - White, Clarence Hudson: correspondence, 1898-1923, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1242-1245)
    - White, Gertrude Schimpf, 1935 (Box 51, Folder 1246)
    - White, Israel L., 1910-13, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1247)
    - White, Jane Felix; White, Ruth, 1906-43 (Box 52, Folder 1248)
    - White, Minor, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 1249)
    - White, Samuel S. III, 1922-27, 1940, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1250)
    - White, Stanford, 1903 Jan 14 (Box 52, Folder 1251)
    - Whitney, Helen Hay, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1252)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1917-46 (Box 52, Folder 1253)
    - Who's Who in American Jewry
      See: Herbert Seligmann (1926 Aug), Boxes 44-45, folders 1044-1056
    - Who's Who in the East, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 1254)
    - Wiener Photo-Klub, 1904-09, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1255)
    - Wiggins, Myra A., 1905-09 (Box 52, Folder 1256)
    - Wilkinson, William J.
      See: Eugene Meyer, Jr., Box 35, folder 817
    - Willard, Eleanor W., 1907 (Box 52, Folder 1257)
    - Willey, Malcolm
    - William Dawson & Sons, Ltd., 1911-16 (Box 52, Folder 1258)
    - Williams, Clifford, 1914-36, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1259)
    - Williams, Ruth, 1937-38 (Box 52, Folder 1260)
    - Williams, William Carlos, 1922-43 (Box 52, Folder 1261)
      Contains "Axioms"
    - Williams, William Carlos: letter to Charles Demuth, 1929 May 7 (Box 52, Folder 1262)
    - Willis and Clements, 1896-1916 (Box 52, Folder 1263)
    - Wilmerding, William E.
      See: Obrig Camera Company, Box 37, folder 885
    - Wilson, Edmund, 1930 Mar 14 (Box 52, Folder 1264)
    - Wilson, Gilbert Brown, 1937-43 (Box 52, Folder 1265)
    - Wilson, Hallie Elizabeth, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 1266)
    - Wilson, Margaret Woodrow, 1938, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 1267)
    - Wilson, Mildred P., 1938-44, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1268-1269)
    - Winston, Lydia K., 1938-46, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1270)
    - Wolf, Howard A., 1941 (Box 52, Folder 1271)
    - Woodbury, Walter E.
      See: Photographic Times, Box 39, folder 927
    - Woollcott, Alexander, 1933 Mar 13 (Box 52, Folder 1272)
    - Worcester Art Museum, 1905-42 (Box 52, Folder 1273)
    - Workman, Fanny Bullock
      See: F. Bruckmann K.G. (1914), Box 19, folders 420-423
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1935, 1937 (Box 52, Folder 1274)
    - Wright, Stanton Macdonald-
      See: Macdonald-Wright, Stanton: correspondence, box 33, folders 759-762
    - Wright, Willard Huntington, 1915-23, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1275)
    - X.Y.Z. [anonymous critic]
      See: Edward Steichen (1915), Box 46, folders 1091-1097
    - "Y" general, 1910-46 (Box 52, Folder 1276)
    - Yellott, Osborne I., 1900-[06] (Box 52, Folder 1277)
    - Young, Art, 1940, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 1278)
    - Young, Robert R.; Young, Anita O'Keeffe, 1940-41, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1279)
    - Young, Sanborn
      See: Paul Strand (1917), Box 48, folders 1129-1145
    - Zigrosser, Carl, 1921-33, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1280)
      See also: Christl Hechenbleikner, Box 24, folder 560
    - Zimmerman, Walter, 1906-10 (Box 52, Folder 1281)
    - Zirinsky, Julius, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 1282)
    - Zoler, Emil C., 1913-45, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1283-1293)
    - Zoler, Emil C.: letters to De Hirsh Margules, 1929, n.d.
    - Zoler, Emil C.: letters to De Hirsh Margules, 1933-34 (Box 53, Folder 1294)
    - Zorach, William; Zorach, Marguerite, 1916-1922 (Box 53, Folder 1295)
      Includes: poems
    - Zsolnay, Thérèse, 1912-15, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1296)
    - Zubrinsky, I., 1916 Mar 17 (Box 53, Folder 1297)
    - Unidentified correspondents, 1881-1945, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1298)
    - Cancelled checks, 1907-26 (Box 53, Folder 1299)
      Forty checks made out to Caffin, Carles, De Casseres, de Meyer, de Zayas, Dove, Eugene, Fellows, Hartley, Laurvik, Lewis, MacLaughlan, Marin, Matisse, Maurer, Rodin, Smith, Steichen, Van Noppen, Walkowitz, and White
    - Exhibition lists, 1909, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1300)
      Unidentified lists of works, primarily photographs, gathered for exhibition; also one list of names and addresses
    - Miscellaneous receipts, reports and medical prescriptions, 1900-26, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1301)
      Includes: repair of tricycle and one-week stay in Paris hotel
  - STIEGLITZ FAMILY LETTERS
    - Cromwell, Georgia Engelhard, 1919-45, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1302-1303)
    - Davidson, Elizabeth Stieglitz: precis of letters, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1304)
    - Davidson, Elizabeth Stieglitz and Donald: correspondence, 1910-41, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1305-1308)
      See also: John Weichsel, Box 51, folder 1228
    - Engelhard, Agnes Stieglitz, 1882-1945, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1309)
      See also: Georgia Engelhard Cromwell (1919-24), Box 54, folders 1302-1303
      See also: Selma Stieglitz Schubart, Box 55, folders 1328-1329
    - Engelhard, George Herbert, 1907-38 (Box 54, Folder 1310)
    - Gertler, Ann Straus: precis of letters, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1311)